“擁有命運之矛的人將掌握世界的命運”
命運之矛自從二戰之后就下落不明
（墨西哥）
曼紐爾
Manuel.
曼紐爾！
Manuel!
曼紐爾
Manuel.
片名：《地獄神探》
（洛杉磯）
我想……
l think. . . .
我給你找著了一個
l think l found you one.
這次我可是給你打電話了
Look, l called you, right?
我一發現自己搞不定
就馬上給你打電話了，約翰
Soon as l couldn't pull it out myself,
l called you, John.
別擔心，沒事的
我們必須得把她綁上，你明白嗎？
lt's okay, it's okay.
We had to tie her down, okay?
沒事的
lt's okay.
我是康斯坦丁
This is Constantine.
約翰·康斯坦丁
你這混蛋
John Constantine, asshole.
當然
Sure.
怎么了？
What the hell?
我需要一面鏡子
l need a mirror.
快去拿！
至少要3英尺高
Now. At least 3 feet high.
愣著干嘛，快去拿啊！
Move! Go, now!
我是克雷默
This is Kramer.
查斯·克雷默
你這混蛋
Chas Kramer, asshole.
混蛋
Asshole.
什么？哦，我是克雷默
查斯·克雷默，混蛋
What? Oh, this is Kramer.
Chas Kramer, asshole.
- 查斯！
- 什么事？
-Chas!
-What?
- 把車挪開
- 為什么？
-Move the car.
-Why?
叫你挪你就挪！
Move the damn car!
“查斯，把車挪開”
''Chas, move the car. ''
好吧，挪了
There, car's moved.
把鏡子舉起來，對著床
Lift it up over the bed.
把那頭系牢
亨內斯，從上面拉過去
Tie that end off.
Hennessy, over the top.
把你們的眼睛閉上
不管發生什么都別睜開
Close your eyes.
And whatever happens, don't look.
不！
No!
現身吧
Show yourself.
來笑一個，你這傻X
Smile pretty, you vain prick.
操你媽！
For your boss.
拉！
Pull it!
媽媽？
Ma? Ma?
我說得沒錯吧，約翰，給你找著一個
是不是？
Like l said, l found you something,
didn't l, John? Didn't l?
那儿怎么了？
What happened in there?
最近會議很多吧
Going to a lot of meetings, l see.
鬧得我都睡不著
Keeps the voices out so l can sleep.
我得睡覺，約翰
l have to sleep, John.
我需要幫助，神父
l need some help, Father.
你？
You do?
要我幫助？
From me?
什么樣的……？
What kind of--?
- 听著，我……
- 你那种驅魔術不對
-Hey, listen, l--
-That exorcism wasn't right.
听著廣播
Listen to the ether.
如果有什么异常，一定要告訴我
Anything unusual, you let me know.
來吧，你不需要它的保護
它今天可能還會回來
Come on, you don't need its protection.
lt'll be like back in the day.
或許几天
A few days.
好吧
Okay.
好吧，為了你，約翰
Okay. For you, John.
約翰，你明知這不是我的車
John, why would you do that
if you know it's not my car?
- 我告訴過你讓你挪開的
- 你是告訴過我
-l told you to move it.
-You did tell me to move it. . .
可是如果你告訴我
你要扔下來一個裝著魔鬼的300磅的鏡子
. . .but if you'd said you were dropping
a 300-pound mirror with a demon. . .
我會把車挪得更遠一點
. . .l would've moved it further, John.
- 去阿爾瓦拉多大街
- 好的先生，我知道怎么走
-Take Alvarado.
-Yeah, thank you. l know what to take.
你有沒有考慮過，如果多告訴我一些事情
說不定我能幫上忙呢？
You ever think if you told me more now
that maybe l could help out?
- 沒有？
- 沒有
-No?
-Nope.
沒有？
Nope?
當然是——沒有
Of course it's a nope.
保佑我，神父，我有罪
Bless me, Father, for l have sinned.
我已經……
It's been...
有兩個禮拜沒來忏悔了
... two weeks since my last confession.
今天我殺了個人
l killed a man today.
又一個
Another one.
我甚至連他長什么樣都沒看清
l didn't even see his face, l just. . .
就扣下了扳机
接著他就死了
. . .pulled the trigger, and he went away.
大多數警察20年都不開一槍
Most cops go 20 years
without firing their guns.
而我卻總是知道
這些家伙藏在哪儿
Why do I always know
where these guys are?
該朝哪儿瞄准，什么時候開槍
Where to aim, when to fire.
神父，我在想
會不會是我有什么問題？
I'm wondering, is there
something wrong with me, Father?
被詛咒了？
Something damned?
上帝自有安排
他給我們每個人都安排好了
God has a plan for you.
He has a plan for us all.
別讓罪惡吞沒了你的信念
You mustn 't let your faith
be overshadowed by guilt.
是的，我在努力
Yeah, I'm trying.
一直都在努力
I'm trying real hard.
伊莎貝爾
Isabel.
我所戰胜的東西
Things l've beaten.
大多數人听都沒听說過
Things most people never even heard of.
可是現在呢
我卻要被這玩意儿搞定
And now l'm gonna be done in by this.
你也不是第一個了，約翰
Wouldn't be the first, John.
得了吧，萊絲
Come on, Les.
你救過我一次
這次也可以，對嗎？
You saved me before,
you can do it again, right?
癌細胞已經擴散了
This is aggressive.
20年前，你不想來這儿
Twenty years ago,
you didn't wanna be here.
現在你又不想离開
Now you don't wanna leave.
你還抽
Yeah, that's a good idea.
約翰，你真的需要准備一下了
John, you really need to prepare.
- 安排后事吧
- 沒必要
-Make arrangements.
-No need.
我很清楚自己何去何從
l already know exactly where l'm going.
- 早
- 早上好
-Morning.
-Good morning.
- 早上好
- 探長
-Good morning.
-Detective.
- 不，不不
- 安吉拉，等等
-No, no, no.
-Angela, wait.
你還是別看了，好嗎？別看了
You don't need to see this, okay? No.
大家先回避一下
Give us the room, please.
伊莎貝爾
lsabel.
她從屋頂上掉下來的？
She fell from the roof?
她跳下來的
She jumped.
- 不可能
- 听著
-No.
-Look. . .
我知道這很難接受
可她有病
. . .l know it's hard to accept.
She was sick.
- 伊莎貝爾不會自殺的
- 安吉
-lsabel wouldn't kill herself.
-Angie.
- 她不會自殺的
- 探長
-She wouldn't kill herself.
-Detective.
- 皮瑞爾德
- 探長
-Period.
-Detective.
皮瑞爾德！
Period!
安吉，監控錄像都拍下來了
Angie, there were security cameras.
- 等一下，是下去么？
- 如果我有辦法，當然不想“下去”
-Hold the door. You going down?
-Not if l can help it.
有新案子？
A new case?
什么大案子？
是你期待已久的嗎？
The big score? The mother lode?
The one you've been waiting for?
- 少奉承我
- 習慣了
-Humor me.
-Don't l always?
哦，這是……
太感激了，謝謝
Oh, yeah, that's--
Much obliged. Thank you.
最近還好嗎，約翰？
How you feeling, John?
看看有什么新的貨色
So, what's new?
教皇遇刺時留下的子彈碎屑
Bullet shavings from
the assassination attempt on the pope. . .
采自約旦河的圣水針劑
. . .holy-water ampoules
from the River Jordan. . .
還有……哦，這個你肯定喜歡
從阿米蒂維勒村找來的尖叫甲虫
（譯者注：參考電影"The Amityville Horror"）
. . .and-- Oh, you'll love this.
--screech beetle from Amityville.
是啊，對你來說很有趣
可對“下面”的東西來說，這就像黑板上釘釘
Yeah, it's funny to you, but to the
fallen, that's like nails on a chalkboard.
你和虫子，到底是什么關系？
What is it, exactly, with you and bugs?
我只是喜歡它們
l just like them.
是啊，誰不喜歡？
Yeah. Who doesn't?
悠著點，大英雄
Yeah, easy there, hero.
- 這是“龍之息”
- 我還以為你再也搞不到了呢
-That's dragon's breath.
-l thought you couldn't get it anymore.
是這樣，我朋友的朋友……
Yeah, well, l know a guy
who knows a guy.
好吧，這次是什么行動？
So, what's the action?
我剛把一個魔兵
從一個小女孩的身体里赶出來
l just pulled a soldier demon
out of a little girl.
看起來好像它想要复活
Looked like it was trying
to come through.
我懂你的意思
Yeah, l know how it sounds.
可是約翰，我們對他們來說
只不過是掌中的玩偶
No, we're finger puppets
to them, John. . .
而不是某种入口
. . .not doorways.
他們可以操縱我們
但不能穿透結界進到我們的世界中
They can work us, but they can't
come through onto our plane.
還是查一下卷軸吧
看看以前有沒有先例
Check the scrolls anyway.
See if there's any precedent.
沒問題，約翰
Sure thing, John.
還有什么事嗎？
Anything else?
你那里有沒有什么可以……？
Wouldn't happen to have
anything for a--?
免費的
（譯者注：止咳藥）
On the house.
好吧，我有個問題
我還得做你的奴隸到几時？
All right, question. How much longer
do l have to be your slave, John?
你不是我的奴隸，查斯
You're not my slave, Chas.
你是我非常賞識的徒弟
You're my very appreciated apprentice.
就像湯托和羅賓一樣
Like Tonto or Robin.
還有那個胖哥身邊的小家伙
Or that skinny fellow
with the fat friend.
好吧，那我除了開車之外
就不能干點別的了么？
Right. So then why don't l apprentice
something besides driving, then, John?
約翰？約翰
John? John.
很高興和你談話，約翰
l love our little talks, John.
您的外套，康斯坦丁先生
May l take your coat, Mr. Constantine?
不用了，謝謝
我一會儿就走
No, thanks,
l'm not gonna be staying long.
- 這位女士，您呢？
- 哦不用了，我也一會儿就走
-How about you, ma'am?
-Oh, no, l'm not staying long either.
我真的要和他說話
有重要的事
l really need to speak with him.
lt's important.
先到先得
First come, first served.
看來你到哪儿都是這么粗魯
So you're rude no matter where you are.
- 神父
- 你好
-Father.
-Hi.
- 帶來什么新消息了
- 是的，剛和主教談過
-You have news. Yes.
-Yes, l spoke with the bishop.
我知道你要什么，孩子
l know what you want, son.
你那雙無所不見的眼睛還盯著我呢
加百列？
（譯者注：替上帝把好消息報告世人的天使）
Still keeping your all-seeing eye
on me, Gabriel?
承蒙夸獎
l'm flattered.
我可以告訴你一些
Well, l could offer something. . .
關于牧羊人是怎樣
帶領他最不听話的羊群的故事
. . .about how a shepherd leads
even the most wayward of his flock. . .
可這听起來也許不夠真誠
. . .but it might sound disingenuous.
她應該得到天主教的葬禮
神父，求你了
She has to have a Catholic funeral,
Father. She has to.
- 安杰拉，她犯的是不可饒恕的大罪
- 她不是自殺的
-Angela, it's still considered a mortal sin.
-She didn't commit suicide.
可主教不這么想
你知道教規的
The bishop believes otherwise.
You know the rules.
哦，教規
Oh, rules.
神父
Father.
戴維
David.
她是伊莎貝爾
This is lsabel.
她惟一相信的愛她的人就是上帝
God was the only one
she ever believed loved her.
求你了
Please.
恕我無能為力
l'm sorry.
最近我看到一些异常的靈异活動
l've been seeing some unusual
soul traffic lately.
也許你能考慮再給我點時間
You might consider
giving me an extension.
我可以為你們這邊幫些忙
l could do your side some good
these days.
你還在為進入天堂積德呢？
You still trying to buy your way
into heaven?
沒見我赶走多少小鬼嗎？
What about the minions l've sent back?
- 光憑這個，就應該保證我能進天堂了
- 我跟你說過多少次了？
-That alone should guarantee my entry.
-How many times have l told you?
靠這樣是進不了天堂的
That's not the way this works.
為什么？我為他做的還不夠多嗎？
Why, haven't l served him enough?
- 他到底想要我怎么樣？
- 很簡單
-What does he want from me?
-Only the usual.
獻身，信仰
Self-sacrifice, belief.
- 哦，我信！我對天發誓
- 不，不，你自己心里有數
-Oh, l believe, for chrissake.
-No, no, you know.
其中的區別你也能看見
And there's a difference. You've seen.
我并沒有要求看見
我生下來就被詛咒了
l never asked to see.
l was born with this curse.
約翰，這是天賦
A gift, John.
而你只是用自私的行動把它浪費了
One that you've squandered
on selfish endeavors.
我把魔鬼從女孩的身体里赶走
l'm pulling demons out of little girls.
這是為了誰？
Who's that for?
你所做的一切都是為了你自己
Everything you've ever done,
you've only ever done for yourself.
為了積德好進入天堂
To earn your way
back into his good graces.
不可能的規則，無盡的約束
lmpossible rules, endless regulations. . .
誰上天，誰入地
為什么
. . .who goes up, who goes down
and why.
你一點都不理解我們
You don't even understand us.
你才應該入地獄
你這個雜种
You're the one who should go
to hell, half-breed.
為什么是我，加百列？
Why me, Gabriel?
這完全是因為我自己的緣故，是不是？
lt's personal, isn't it?
因為去教堂去得太少
也不怎么祈禱
l didn't go to church enough,
l didn't pray enough. . .
還舍不得往募捐箱里放上5塊錢
是不是？
. . .l was 5 bucks short
in the collection plate. Why?
你這么年輕就要死
You are going to die young. . .
是因為你從15歲起就每天要吸30根煙
. . .because you smoked 30 cigarettes
a day since you were 1 5.
而你之所以要去地獄
And you're going to go to hell. . .
是因為你所過的生活
. . .because of the life you took.
你很失敗
You're fucked.
至少在外面感覺還不錯
At least it's nice out.
他總是一點幽默感都沒有
He always had a rotten sense of humor.
他的笑話一點都不好笑
And his punch lines are killers.
約翰！
John!
康斯坦丁，下雨哪！
約翰，嗨！
Constantine, it's raining! John! Hey!
凶手的后院里發現埋藏著22具女尸
Twenty-two women were found buried
in the assailant's back yard.
尸体受到嚴重的摧殘
警察的辨認工作……
So much damage had been done
to the bodies, police had to match....
据警察說
她的身体曾被穿刺超過100次
Police report she had been
physically penetrated...
然后被活埋
...over 1 00 times and buried alive.
……被發現鎖在冷藏庫中
頭部嚴重受傷，器官……
--found locked in a storage freezer,
his head severed and his organs....
他把霍莉的身体塞入……
He stuffed Holly's body into....
- 受到不明強暴的尸体……
- 他使用了一把小手鋸……
-The bodies ravished by the unknown....
-He used a small handsaw....
頭顱几乎被砍下來……
眼珠都被挖了出來
Had nearly decapitated....
Even his eyes were gouged out.
伊莎貝爾
Isabel.
（精神病院的自殺事件）
我很抱歉，妹妹
l'm so sorry, lzzy.
康斯坦丁
Constantine.
道森
Dodson.
喂？
Hello?
喂
Hello.
喂？
Hello?
嗨，老兄
能借個火嗎
Hey. Hey, buddy, got a light?
別多管閒事，驅魔人
Should've minded
your own business, exorcist.
我知道你要去哪儿，約翰
你要去米耐那儿
l know where you're going, John.
You're going to Midnite's.
希望你呆在車里
You're supposed to wait in the cab.
那儿是鬼魂的避難所
我記得在書上讀到過，約翰
lt's a haven for those who rise and fall.
l remember reading about this, John.
- 你讀書讀得太多了，那是個酒吧
- 酒吧？
-You read too much, kid. lt's a bar.
-lt's a bar?
是酒吧，米耐老爹是個樂善好施的人
他曾經發誓堅守中立
lt's a bar. Papa Midnite is a crusader for
good. He swore the oath of neutrality.
- 約翰，他可是傳奇人物
- 是的
-John, the man's a legend.
-Yeah.
你能帶我進去嗎？
約翰，求求你
Can you please get me
into this bar, John, please?
求你了，約翰，行嗎？
l'm begging you, John, please?
- 好吧，你可以進去
- 我可以進去？
-Sure, you can get in.
-l can get in?
如果你能進去的話
lf you can get in.
如果我能……？
是熊？還是云中的兩只鴨子？
lf l can get--? lt's a bear, though, right?
Or two ducks in a cloud?
長凳上的兩只青蛙
Two frogs on a bench.
不，我是和剛才那個人一起的……
No, no, l'm with the guy you just--
約翰！約翰！
John! John!
我是和他一起的
l'm with him, though.
穿著裙子的老鼠
Rat in a dress.
當然，穿著裙子的老鼠
Of course it is. Rat in a dress.
我只是試試，只是試試
l'm just testing. l'm just testing.
不用站起來了
Don't get up.
好久不見了
You've been absent some time.
又有什么圣物要賣嗎？
Have you come here with relics to sell?
沒有，現在不干那個了
太忙了
No, l'm out of that now.
l've been too busy.
終于發現造假對你的健康不利了？
Perhaps peddling forgeries has ended up
being bad for your health.
米耐，上帝啊……
Midnite, Jesus. . .
……我想這件事是真的
. . .l thought the thing was authentic.
我知道了
l see now.
你的身体不好是因為其他原因
多長時間了？
Your health is bad for other reasons.
How long?
几個月吧，可能一年
A few months, maybe a year.
我昨晚好像听到雷聲了
l thought l heard thunder last night.
肯定是撒旦的胃在咆哮
Must have been
Satan's stomach growling.
你的魂要他親自出馬來收
You're the one soul he'd come
up here himself to collect.
我也听說了
So l've heard.
好吧，我想你來這儿
Well, l am most certain
you did not come here. . .
肯定不是想找個有同情心的人來訴苦的
. . .for a sympathetic shoulder
to cry on.
剛才有個魔鬼攻擊了我
就在通往費格羅阿大街的路上
A demon just attacked me,
right out in the open on Figueroa.
他們不喜歡你，約翰
They don't like you, John.
你驅赶了多少個魔鬼？
How many have you
deported back to hell?
米耐，這次不是那种憤怒的雜种
而是實實在在的魔鬼，就在這儿，在我們的世界里
Not some angry half-breed, Midnite.
A full-fledged demon, here, on our plane.
我想我不用提醒你
這是不可能的
Clearly l do not have to remind you
that is impossible.
還有昨天，我見到一個魔兵
And yesterday l saw a soldier demon. . .
試圖從一個小女孩身体里沖破結界
. . .trying to chew its way out
through a little girl.
听著，約翰，魔鬼只能呆在地獄里
天使只能呆在天堂里
Listen, John, demons stay in hell,
angels in heaven. . .
從造物之初就是這樣
. . .the great detente
of the original superpowers.
謝謝你給我上的歷史課，米耐
你真是幫了我大忙了
Thanks for the history lesson, Midnite.
You've been a tremendous help.
現在
Now. . .
我需要使用那把椅子
. . .l need to use the chair.
約翰，你難道忘了
這么做几乎肯定是要沒命的
John, forgetting the fact that it would
almost certainly kill you. . .
你知道我是中立者
. . .you know l am neutral.
只要平衡沒有發生變化
我就保持中立
And as long as the balance
is maintained, l take no sides.
在你當酒吧侍應之前
Before you were a bartender. . .
你曾經是個巫醫
. . .you were one witch doctor
against, what, 30 Ashgar?
- 而我……
- 你是康斯坦丁
-And l--
-You were Constantine.
約翰·康斯坦丁
The John Constantine.
曾經是的
Once.
這次非比尋常，我能感覺得到
This isn't the usual game, l can feel it.
它在逼近
Something's coming.
膽小鬼
Spooky.
巴爾薩澤
Balthazar.
光是那种表情就讓我徹夜難眠
That expression alone
has made my entire night.
我來教你怎么睡覺
l'll make your night.
我現在就把你打回老家去
你這個雜碎！
l'll deport your sorry ass right where
you stand, you half-breed shit!
你知道我這儿的規矩
在我這儿就要按我的規矩來
You know the rules of my house.
While here, you will abide by them.
小約翰
Johnny boy.
听說你快要下來了
Word is you're on your way down.
新鮮的肉啊
Fresh meat.
吮指回味
Finger-licking good.
約翰，我們還有事要談
We have a meeting now, John.
你說什么？我沒听清
What? l didn't catch that.
歡迎加入我的生活
Welcome to my life.
康斯坦丁先生
Mr. Constantine.
- 我們之前……
- 我記得
-l saw you--
-l remember.
- 后來還在……
- 看來咱們還真是有緣
-And then l saw you at the--
-Regular kismet.
能不能容我問几個問題
l'd like to ask you a few questions,
if that would be okay.
現在我不想和任何人說話
l'm not really in the talking mood
right now.
好吧，那光听我說可以嗎？
Well, maybe you could just listen then.
行嗎？
Please?
就知道沒那么簡單
Always a catch.
昨天我妹妹被謀殺了
My sister was murdered yesterday.
- 很遺憾
- 謝了
-Sorry to hear.
-Thanks.
她是雷文斯卡精神病院的病人
從屋頂跳下去死的
She was a patient at Ravenscar.
She jumped off the roof.
剛才好像听你說是謀殺？
Thought you said she was murdered.
是的，伊莎貝爾不可能自殺的
Yeah, well, lsabel wouldn't
have taken her own life.
也是，什么樣的精神病人會自殺呢？
Yeah, what kind of mental patient
kills herself?
真可怕
That's just crazy.
是這樣的，我听說你在這塊很有名
Look, l've heard your name
around the precinct.
我知道你活動的圈子
超自然，鬼神學，驅魔……
l know the circles you travel in.
The occult, demonology, exorcisms.
就在我妹妹被殺之前
她得了嚴重的妄想症
Just before my sister was committed,
she became deeply paranoid.
她開始談論魔鬼，天使
She started talking about demons,
angels.
我想她是被什么人影響了
康斯坦丁先生
Now, l think someone got to her,
Mr. Constantine.
她肯定是被洗了腦
才會從屋頂上跳下去的
l think they brainwashed her
into stepping off that roof.
某种邪教組織
Some kind of legion or cult.
你分析得很有道理啊
大偵探
Sounds like a theory, detective.
祝你好運
Good luck.
我想以你的背景
至少可以……
l thought with your background,
you could at least. . .
給我指明正确的方向
. . .point me in the right direction.
可以，當然可以
Yeah, okay, sure.
她不是自殺
lt wasn't a suicide.
我妹妹是個虔誠的天主教徒
My sister was a devout Catholic.
你懂嗎？
如果她自己結束自己的生命
Do you understand that?
lf she took her own life--
她的靈魂會直接下地獄
Her soul would go straight to hell. . .
在尖叫中一次又一次地被撕裂
飽受折磨，极度痛苦
. . .where she'd be ripped apart over
and over in screaming, brutal agony. . .
永世不得翻身，對嗎？
. . .for all eternity. That it?
我說得沒錯吧？
That about right?
你他媽的
Goddamn you.
偵探
Detective.
如果我告訴你
上帝和魔鬼打了個賭……
What if l told you that God
and the devil made a wager. . .
他們的賭注就是所有人類的靈魂
你信么？
. . .a kind of standing bet
for the souls of all mankind?
我會告訴你回去找你的醫生
l'd tell you to stay on your meds.
別跟我爭
他們的約定是不能直接涉足人間
Humor me. No direct contact with
humans. That would be the rule.
- 只能施加影響，最后看誰能贏
- 好吧，我不跟你爭
-Just influence. See who would win.
-Okay, l'm humoring you.
- 可是為什么呢？
- 誰知道呢
-Why?
-Who knows.
- 也許只是為了好玩
- 哦，這可真好玩
-Maybe just for the fun of it. No telling.
-Oh, so it's fun.
丈夫打死妻子好玩么？
母親淹死孩子好玩么？
lt's fun when a man beats his wife to
death, when a mother drowns her baby.
你覺得這都歸因于魔鬼？
And you think the devil is responsible?
你錯了，康斯坦丁
是人，人才是魔鬼
People are evil, Mr. Constantine. People.
你說得很對
人性本惡
You're right. We're born
capable of terrible things.
再加上受到其他某种東西的引導……
Then sometimes something else comes
along and gives us just the right nudge.
好吧，謝謝你給我上了一課
Well, this has been real educational. . .
可我不相信有什么魔鬼
. . .but l don't believe in the devil.
你應該相信
就如魔鬼相信你的存在
You should. He believes in you.
只是停電了
lt's a power outage.
不像
Not likely.
- 什么？
- 不能呆在這儿了，快走
-What?
-We should go. Now.
那是什么？
What is that?
翅膀
Wings.
也許是魔爪
Maybe talons.
別開玩笑了，你說什么？
You're kidding. Of what?
一些不該在這儿的東西
Something that's not
supposed to be here.
槍在這儿基本上沒用
That's really not going to help.
- 閉上眼睛
- 為什么？
-Close your eyes.
-Why?
為了你自己
Suit yourself.
誰說魔鬼只呆在地獄里？
Demons stay in hell, huh?
得告訴他們
Tell them that.
別擔心
第一次都是這樣
Don't worry. Happens to everyone
the first time.
那是硫磺
lt's the sulfur.
硫磺
Sulfur.
那些東西是什么？
What were those things?
魔鬼
Demons.
- 被詛咒的食腐怪
- 不，這不可能
-Scavengers of the damned.
-No, no. lt's impossible.
信不信由你
而且我認為它們不是來找我的
Yeah. And l don't think
they were after me.
你真的認為她不是自殺的？
You really believe
she wouldn't commit suicide.
伊莎貝爾？
lsabel?
絕對不信
Never in a million years.
好吧，我們來确認一下
Well, let's be sure.
看看她是不是在地獄里
Let's see if she's in hell.
哦，應該是冷水還是熱水？
Oh, was it supposed to be hot or cold?
放在椅子前面
ln front of the chair.
真不敢相信我居然在干這個
l can't believe l'm doing this.
- 這些都是伊莎貝爾的東西？
- 對
-These are all lsabel's things?
-Yeah.
- 這貓呢？
- 達珂？
-How about the cat?
-Duck?
是啊，怎么了？
Yeah, why?
達珂
Duck.
哦，覺得奇怪是么
Oh, you think that's strange.
貓是很好的動物
Cats are good.
很有靈性
Half in, half out anyway.
如果你要施某种法術或什么的話
lf this is some kind of spell
or something. . .
難道不需要點蜡燭和畫五角星么？
. . .don't you need candles
and a pentagram for it to work?
哦？你有嗎？
Why, do you have any?
- 簡直是瘋了
- 是的
-This is crazy.
-Yes.
你得离開
l need you to leave.
- 為什么？
- 安吉拉，拜托
-l'm sorry?
-Angela, please.
我是說离開這屋子
The apartment.
好吧
Okay.
當心我的貓
Be careful with that cat.
上帝，我恨干這個
God, l hate this part.
- 伊莎貝爾
- 康斯坦丁
-lsabel.
-Constantine.
安吉拉
Angela.
上帝
Jesus.
- 康斯坦丁，你怎么啦？
- 雙胞胎
-Constantine, what--?
-Twins.
上帝，你說什么？
Jesus. What?
- 你們是雙胞胎
- 你說什么？
-You were twins.
-What did you say?
- 她是自殺的
- 什么？
-She killed herself.
-What?
因此被罰入地獄
And she's damned for it.
這怎么可能？
How is this possible?
我得吃點東西
l need to eat.
嗨，嗨！
你在這儿干什么？
Hey! Hey, what are you doing in here?
別激動，哥們儿
Relax, man.
慢點！
Slow down!
這儿他媽的是什么地方？
What the hell kind of place is this?
約翰
John.
我小的時候
能看到一些東西
When l was a kid, l could see things.
一些人類看不到的東西
Things humans aren't supposed to see.
也是不應該看到的東西
Things you shouldn 't have to see.
我父母都是正常人
他們像大多數父母一樣
My parents were normal.
They did what most parents would do.
讓情況變得更糟
They made it worse.
當你覺得再也無法忍受的時候
You think you're crazy long enough. . .
你就會尋找出路
. . .you find a way out.
- 你嘗試自殺？
- 我什么都沒嘗試
-You tried to kill yourself.
-I didn 't try anything.
准确的說，我死過兩分鐘
Officially, I was dead for two minutes.
但是當我跨入另一個世界的時候
But when you cross over. . .
時間就停止了
. . .time stops.
我敢說
地獄里的兩分鐘就像一生那么漫長
Take it from me,
two minutes in hell is a lifetime.
當我重回人世的時候
When l came back. . .
我終于知道
. . .l knew. . .
我能看到的所有的東西都是真實的
. . .all the things l could see were real.
天堂和地獄無處不在
每一堵牆，每一扇窗后面
Heaven and hell are right here.
Behind every wall, every window.
這個世界背后還有一個世界
而我們被夾在中間
The world behind the world,
and we're smack in the middle.
天使和魔鬼都不能逾越
進入我們的世界
Angels and demons can't
cross over onto our plane.
所以，我們看到的就是所謂的“雜种”
So instead we get
what l call half-breeds.
蠱惑者
The influence peddlers.
它們只能在你耳邊煽風點火
但是它的一句話就能給你勇气
They can only whisper in our ears, but
a single word can give you courage...
或者讓你一下子從快樂的巔峰
掉落到痛苦的深淵
...or turn your favorite pleasure
into your worst nightmare.
那些被魔鬼触碰的
Those with the demon 's touch...
比如半天使
是和我們生活在一起的
...like those part angel,
living alongside us.
他們稱之為平衡
They call it the balance.
而我稱之為虛偽的狗屁
l call it hypocritical bullshit.
所以當哪個雜种不守規矩
So when a half-breed breaks the rules. . .
我會直接讓他滾進地獄
. . .l deport their sorry ass
straight back to hell.
這樣的雜种太多了
l don't get them all. . .
我只希望盡量多的除掉一些
讓自己能夠
. . .but l've been hoping to get enough
to ensure my. . .
- 早點退休
- 我不懂
-. . .retirement.
-l don't understand.
我就是在自殺，安吉拉
l'm a suicide, Angela.
當我死的時候，按照規則
我只有一個地方可去
When l die, the rules say
l've got just one place to go.
你是在積德，希望能進天堂
You're trying to buy your way
into heaven.
要是你被關進一個
半數犯人都是你親手抓進去的監獄里
What would you do
if you were sentenced to a prison. . .
你會有什么感覺？
. . .where half the inmates
were put there by you?
我想上帝為我們每個人都安排好了一切
l guess God has a plan for all of us.
小姐
上帝只是一個玩螞蟻的小孩
God's a kid with an ant farm, lady.
他什么都沒安排
He's not planning anything.
在我們小的時候
When we were little. . .
伊莎貝爾也能看到東西
. . .lsabel saw things too.
道森
Dodson.
警衛發現他在摸弄尸体
然后他倉皇跑到街對面
Guard spotted him groping the body,
then he ran across the street.
跑進店里來
把貨架上的酒打開喝了個遍
Came in here, and he had a go
at the entire stock.
不到一分鐘
他就溺死在酒里了
He drowned himself in alcohol
in under a minute.
本可以成為我們教友會的一員的
Could've been a member
of my fraternity.
他跑到這儿來干什么？
Hey, what the hell is he doing here?
沒關系
He's okay.
為什么不給我打電話
狗娘養的
Why didn't you call me,
you son of a bitch?
喂？
Yes?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
什么？
What?
怎么會？
How?
知道了，拜拜
Got it. Bye.
我要看一下伊莎貝爾死亡的現場
l need to see where lsabel died.
請神，占卜，通靈
Seances, Ouija boards, channeling.
父親以為她只是想引人注意
Our father thought she was
just trying to get attention.
可事實上不是
She certainly did that.
她把她看到的東西告訴每一個人
She'd tell everyone about the things
she said she saw.
把母親嚇得半死
She'd scare my mother half to death.
之后几乎一年
她始終一言不發
And then she stopped talking
for almost a year.
所以你們把她送到這儿來了
So you had her committed.
是的
Yeah.
有多長時間了？
How long?
兩個星期
Two weeks.
這一次
This time.
她的病情時好時坏
最近又惡化了
She'd get better, and then she'd
get worse. Recently, a lot worse.
那個死者手掌上刻的符號
That symbol that was cut
in the dead guy's hand. . .
會不會和這有關？
. . .does it have something to do
with this?
約翰，別忘了我是警察
l'm a cop, John, remember?
一個人不可能什么都沒留下
就這么跳樓自殺的
You don't walk off the roof of a building
without leaving something behind.
而我已經把她所有的遺物都給你看過了
不過你盡管找
And l showed you everything
she left behind in that box, but feel free.
也許她留下了一些
警察找不到的東西
Maybe she left something else.
Not something a cop would find.
一些只有你才能找到的東西
Something just for you.
你們是雙胞胎，安吉拉
雙胞胎的想法是相似的
You were her twin, Angela.
Twins tend to think alike.
- 我不像我的妹妹
- 但你曾經是的
-l'm not like my sister.
-But you were once.
當你們還是孩子的時候
When you were kids.
當你們每時每刻形影不离的時候
When you'd spend every second
with each other.
你說一句，她就能接下句
你受傷了，她就會哭
You'd start a sentence, she'd finish it.
You'd get hurt, she'd cry.
那是很久以前了
That was a long time ago.
那种聯系不會這么輕易就消失的
That kind of bond doesn't
just disappear.
這儿什么都沒有
There is nothing here.
- 得了吧
- 她在這間屋子里籌划了自己的死
-Hey. Come on.
-She planned her death in this room.
她是在這儿想出來的
就在你所站的地方
She thought it up right here.
Right where you're standing.
她知道你會來
她指望你能見她所見
She knew you'd come. She counted
on you to see what she saw. . .
感她所感
知她所知
. . .feel what she felt,
know what she knew.
- 安吉拉，她做了什么？
- 我怎么會知道？
-What did she do, Angela?
-How should l know?
- 安吉拉，她做了什么？
- 我不知道
-What did she do, Angela?
-l don't know.
- 換了你會怎么做？
- 我不知道
-What would you do?
-l don't know.
安吉拉，她做了什么？
你知道的，她到底做了什么？
What did she do, Angela? You know
what she did. What did she do, Angela?
你知道的！
你為什么不敢說？她做了什么？
You know what she did. What are
you afraid of? What did she do?
- 她做了什么？
- 我不知道！
-What did she do?
-l don't know!
我們小的時候
When we were girls. . .
喜歡互相給對方留密信
. . .we would leave each other messages.
用光
ln light.
或者在窗戶上
ln breath.
用嘴哈气
On the windows.
約翰，歌林多書中沒有17章啊
John, there is no 1 7th act
in Corinthians.
地獄圣經里，歌林多書有21章
Corinthians goes to 21 acts
in the Bible in hell.
地獄里也有圣經
They have Bibles in hell.
描繪了另一幅“啟示錄”
Paints a different view of Revelations.
地獄圣經中說
世界不會在上帝的手中終結
Says the world will not end
by God's hand...
而是會在黑暗中重生
...but be reborn in the embrace
of the damned.
到那時……
Though if you ask me...
就是人間煉獄了
. . .fire's fire.
16章29節，16章30節
1 6:29, 1 6:30.
哦，天哪
果然不妙
Oh, my, this is certainly not good.
“子之罪定會超越父之罪”
''The sins of the father would only
be exceeded by the sins of the son. ''
- 誰的儿子？
- 但是他不可能逾越結界
-Whose son?
-But he can't cross over, B.
- 結界是不可能逾越的
- 誰的儿子？上帝的儿子？
-lmpossible to cross over.
-Whose son? God's son?
不，是另一個
魔鬼也有儿子
No, the other one. Devil had a son too.
在這儿
Here it is.
這是魔鬼之子曼蒙的標志
This is the sign of Mammon. . .
哦等一下，這儿說……
. . .the son of the devil.
Well, hold on, it says here--
- 比曼？
- 在
-Beeman?
-Yeah.
抱歉，我……
抱歉，不，我在
Sorry, l'm--
l'm sorry, no, l'm right here.
上面說曼蒙對他父親的規矩不耐煩了
lt says Mammon has no patience
for his father's rule. . .
渴望建立一個屬于他自己的
火与血的王國
. . .and yearns to forge his own kingdom
of fire and blood.
沒錯，曼蒙是我們最不愿意見到
Yeah. Mammon would be
the last demon. . .
出現在我們世界里的魔鬼
. . .we'd ever want crossing over
to our plane.
等等，等等，听我讀下去
可是似乎存在某种漏洞
No, wait, wait, wait. l'm reading.
Seems to be a loophole.
就知道沒那么簡單
Always a catch.
這里說到
曼蒙首先要附身于一個非常強大的通靈者
lt says first Mammon would have to
possess a very, very powerful psychic.
- 伊莎貝爾
- 但這還不夠
-lsabel.
-But that wouldn 't be enough.
要穿越結界
曼蒙還需要神的協助
To cross over, Mammon would need
divine assistance.
也就是說需要上帝的幫助
To cross over, Mammon would need
the help of God.
- 上帝的幫助？
- 上面說……
-The help of God?
-It says--
- 比曼？
- 約翰，听著
-Beeman?
-John, look. . .
我知道你從來都沒有什么信念
你從來都不愿意……
. . .l know you've never had much faith,
you've never had much reason to. . .
可這并不意味著你的心里
...but that doesn 't mean
that we don 't have faith...
不存在信念
. . .in you.
比曼？比曼？
Beeman? Beeman?
開快點
Drive. Fast.
比曼！
Beeman!
硫磺
Sulfur.
比曼！
Beeman!
不只是伊莎貝爾
Wasn't just lsabel.
我以前也能見到東西
l used to see things too.
可是……
But. . .
- 你已經知道了，是不是？
- 回家去，安吉拉
-. . .you already knew that, didn't you?
-Go home, Angela.
我要把事情搞清楚
l need to understand.
這些事情你最好不要知道
相信我
You don't wanna know
what's out there, trust me.
我比伊莎貝爾強
l'm stronger than lsabel.
你的妹妹接受了她的天賦
而你拒絕了，還是拒絕比較好
Your sister embraced her gift,
you denied yours. Denial is a better idea.
這也是為什么你還活著的原因
如果你繼續跟著我，就難說了
lt's why you're still alive.
Stick with me, that will change.
我不想再多個鬼魂跟著我
l don't need another ghost
following me.
約翰，他們殺了我妹妹！
John, they killed my sister.
我宁愿死的那個是我
l'd trade places with her if l could.
我過去一直假裝自己沒有這种能力
l used to pretend that l didn't.
什么都看不見
That l didn't see things.
然后
And. . .
到我們10歲的時候
父母開始強迫她吃安定藥
. . .by the time we were 1 0,
they started forcing her to take. . .
并且接受治療
. . .antipsychotics. . .
當那些東西出現的時候
. . .and have treatments.
They would come for her. . .
她總是看著我
對我說：“告訴他們啊”
. . .and she'd look at me,
and she'd say to me, ''Tell them.
“安吉，為什么你不告訴他們
你也能看見？”
Why don't you tell them, Angie,
that you can see them too?''
可我卻撒了謊
But l lied.
我說：
l said:
“我什么都沒看見”
''l don't see anything. ''
直到有一天
Until one day. . .
我終于真的看不見了
. . .l finally stopped seeing.
我拋棄了她，約翰
l abandoned her, John.
我讓她孤立無援
l left her all alone.
我必須得看到她所看到的東西
l need to see what she saw.
請你幫幫我
Please.
這么做，可就沒法回頭了
You do this, there's no turning back.
你看見了他們
You see them. . .
他們也看見了你
. . .they see you.
明白嗎？
Understand?
明白
Yeah.
好吧
Sure.
我必須把所有的衣服都脫了么？
還是可以穿著？
So do l have to take the rest of
my clothes off, or can l leave them on?
約翰？
John?
我在考慮
l'm thinking.
約翰？
John?
穿著吧
On is fine.
- 為什么用水？
- 水是万能的通道
-So why water?
-lt's a universal conduit.
可以幫助穿越結界
Lubricates the transition
from one plane to another.
- 接著問我地獄里有沒有水
- 地獄里有沒有水？
-Now ask me if there's water in hell.
-ls there water in hell?
坐下
Sit.
通常只要身体的一部分浸入水中就可以了
Normally, only a portion of the body
has to be suspended. . .
但是你想來個速成的
. . .but you wanted the crash course.
是的，我要速成的
Yeah, l wanted the crash course.
那么……
So. . . .
那會怎么樣？
So, what's gonna happen?
躺下
Lie down.
- 躺下？什么意思？
- 你必須完全浸入水中
-What do you mean lie down?
-You have to be fully submerged.
要多長時間？
For how long?
能堅持多久就多久
As long as it takes.
深吸一口气
Take a deep one.
哦，上帝
Oh, God.
哦，上帝，所有這些人
Oh, God, all those people.
哦，伊莎貝爾
Oh, lsabel.
我總是知道
l've always known.
我總是知道它們在哪儿
我總是知道如何找到它們
l've always known where they are.
l've always known where to find them. . .
朝哪儿瞄准，在哪儿躲避
. . .where to aim and where to duck. . .
我總是知道它們在哪儿
. . .and l've always known
where they were.
我知道那不是運气
l've always known that it wasn't luck.
我一直都知道……
Always known that it wasn't luck.
l've always known. . . .
我一直都知道我能看見
l've always known that l could see.
安吉拉
Angela.
有人來過
Someone was here.
那是他留下的
lt was his.
轉動著
Rolling.
不是球
Not a ball.
是某种小一點的東西
Something smaller.
閃著光
Shiny.
巴爾薩澤
Balthazar.
對不起
Sorry.
要殺了他嗎？？
Can you just kill him?
那平衡怎么辦？
What about the balance?
當這些雜种開始殺我朋友的時候
平衡就已經被破坏了
Half-breed tipped the scales
when he started killing my friends.
我只是在天平的另一邊加些砝碼而已
l'm just adding some counterweight.
約翰，我真的很想……
John, l really want--
把它當作防彈衣
Think of it as a bulletproof vest.
我要和你一起去
l'm coming with you.
你得呆在車里
You're staying in the car.
火？我就是火里生的
Fire? l was born of this.
你這個爛雜种，告訴我
曼蒙到底要怎樣跨越結界？
How's Mammon crossing over,
you half-breed piece of shit?
這樣更好，更自然
That's better. Au naturel.
“呆在車里”
''Stay in the car. ''
“在這儿等”
''Wait here. ''
受不了你
Men.
別抗拒，小約翰
Don't fight it, Johnny boy.
好好享受
Enjoy it.
我們馬上就能見到你了
We'll see you very soon.
你說錯了
Not really, no.
這回你跑不掉的
你會回到地獄里去
You can't cheat it this time.
You're going back to hell.
沒錯
True.
可你卻回不去了
But you're not.
- 你要干嘛？
- 我要給你做最后的超度
-What are you doing?
-l'm reading you your last rites.
別對我用治療咒語
Spare me your remedial incantations.
你想知道真正被寬恕以后
會是什么樣嗎？
You do know what it is
to truly be forgiven?
被接納進入神的王國
To be welcomed
into the Kingdom of God.
天堂里的魔鬼
Demon in heaven.
真想看看那時的情景
l'd love to be a fly on that wall.
你不是牧師，你沒有法力
You're not a priest. You have no power.
那你告訴我曼蒙打算怎樣沖破結界
Just tell me how Mammon
is crossing over. . .
我就讓你滾回你的狗窩去
. . .and you can go back
to your shithole.
好啊，不說是吧
Okay, Bally, enjoy it.
“愿主怜憫你，饒恕你所有的罪孽”
''May God have mercy on you
and grant you the pardon of all your sins.
“不管犯下什么樣的罪孽
都饒恕你，讓你升入天堂”
Whose soever sins you remit on Earth,
they are remitted unto them in heaven. ''
- 快說，他要怎樣沖破結界？
- 不
-How? How's he doing it?
-No.
不，我不能說
No, l can't.
“讓你的子民找到通往天國的大門……”
Grant your child entry
into thy kingdom. . .
“以圣父、圣子和圣靈之名”
. . .in the name of the Father and the Son
and the Holy Spirit.
阿門！
Amen!
上帝的血
The blood of God.
他找到了
He found it.
只要殺死了上帝之子
Whatever killed the son of God. . .
就能讓魔鬼之子复活
. . .will give birth to the son of the devil.
順便說一句
By the way. . .
只有經過赦免才能得到寬恕
. . .you have to ask for absolution
to be forgiven. . .
笨蛋
. . .asshole.
我的任務已經完成了
My work here is done.
- 你笑什么？
- 我的任務就是她
-What are you laughing at?
-She was my only mission. . .
而你正好把她帶來了
. . .and you brought her right to us.
干嘛走這么快
是不是發現了什么？
So does this walking fast
mean you've found something?
耶穌不是在十字架上被釘死的
而是被一個戰士的矛刺死的
Jesus didn't die from being nailed to a
cross. He was killed by a soldier's spear.
命運之矛
The Spear of Destiny.
我是個天主教徒，約翰
我知道耶穌受難的故事
l'm a Catholic, John.
l know the Crucifixion story.
按您的吩咐，我引出了她的姐姐
l drew out the sister as you asked.
她的靈力已經被喚醒
She's been made flush and ready.
好強的能量
So much power.
如果您能讓我复活
我愿意為您效忠
Now, if you grant me my resurrection,
l shall serve.
等等，我們說好的
Wait. But l did as we agreed.
不，不！
No. Please. No!
比曼說過
曼蒙需要神的幫助才能跨越結界
Beeman said Mammon needed
divine assistance to cross over.
看來那就是上帝唯一的儿子的血
How's the blood of God's only son?
矛上的血跡
The stains on the spear.
- 是的
- 那么說他找到了矛
-Yeah.
-So he gets the spear.
他還要找一個很強的通靈者
He still has to locate
a powerful psychic.
已經有了
Not really.
雙胞胎
Twins.
護身符呢？
Where's the amulet?
我不知道
肯定是落在車上了
l don't know,
l must have left it in the--
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我不知道，只是覺得……
l don't know, l just feel--
- 梯子上的鳥
- 抱歉
-Bird on a ladder.
-Sorry.
- 在這儿等
- 好的
-Wait here.
-Yeah.
現在誰是穿裙子的老鼠了？啊？
狗娘養的
Who's a rat in a dress now, huh, bitch?
你連最后一點理智都沒了么
Have you lost what little mind you have?
別動
Don't.
我需要用那張椅子
l need to use the chair.
我不會幫任何一邊
l offer no aid to one side or the other.
- 平衡
- 去他媽的平衡
-The balance.
-Screw the balance.
你敢？在我這儿？
You dare? ln my house?
這也叫中立嗎？狗屁！
ls this neutral? Bullshit.
米耐，你是唯一一個還在按規矩做的人！
You're the only one still playing
by the rules, Midnite.
當你保持中立的時候
人們卻在死去
And while you've been imitating
Switzerland, people are dying.
亨尼斯，比曼，他們曾經都是你的朋友
你不記得了么？
Hennessy, Beeman, they were
your friends once too, remember?
我需要你的幫助！
l need your help!
就當是最后的請求
Consider it a last request.
你太冒險了
You play a dangerous game.
這件襯衫可要200美元
Two-hundred-dollar shirt, by the way.
那個小畜牲早就想走出
他父親的陰影了
That little shit has been trying to climb
out of his father's shadow for eons.
不敢想象要是他沖破結界的話
世界會變成什么樣
l'd hate to think what he would do
to this world if he ever broke through.
都忘了它有這么大
Forgot how big it was.
在紐約新新監獄里
這張椅子曾經拷問了200個靈魂
Two hundred souls passed through
this wood and steel at Sing Sing.
是的
Yeah.
哪邊是東？
Which way's east?
多久沒沖浪了？
How many years since you've surfed?
就像騎自行車
Like riding a bike.
沒那么輕松
No, not really.
希望這不是為了那女孩
Tell me this isn't about the girl.
絕對主要不是為了那女孩
Definitely mostly not about the girl.
好冷
Cold.
來一口？
Little flavor?
- 准備好了？
- 不
-Sure about this?
-No.
米耐！
Midnite!
- 找到了么？
- 找到了
-Any luck?
-That's a word for it.
老天，這不是米耐老爹嗎？
Holy shit. You're Papa Midnite,
aren't you?
你到底打算怎么用這些？
要离得很近才行
And how exactly do you intend
on getting close enough to use these?
她的周圍肯定有人守衛
Well, they did not leave her unguarded.
當雜种的外皮被圣水澆裂之后
Half-breeds are most vulnerable. . .
他們是非常脆弱的
. . .when their outer skin is breached
by holy water.
可以用某些圣物
特別是伊斯塔利亞十字架
Certain objects, most notably
either of the two crosses of lsteria. . .
即使是沒有正式受命的牧師
也可以用它來把……
. . .have been used by even
the unordained to bless. . .
普通的水……
. . .commonly occurring waters. . .
甚至是雨水，變成圣水
. . .even rain.
也許如果……
Maybe if. . . .
如果沒有為比賽做好准備
干坐在候補席上也是沒用的，對嗎？
There's no use sitting on the bench
if you're not ready to play, right?
我們為什么不從櫥柜里
拿一支施有魔法的十字架
You wouldn't have one of those
enchanted crosses here in a cabinet. . .
帶在身上用呢？
. . .maybe we could take with us?
約翰，我無意冒犯
我只是提點建議，我覺得……
Look, John, no offense, l just don't think
that it's a great idea, you know. . .
你這樣單槍匹馬去拯救世界
這么做并不聰明
. . .you going on a solo mission
to save the world. That's my vote.
我不知道他怎么想
可是……
l don't know what pops thinks,
but that's--
把他帶上吧，約翰
完事之后再把他殺了
Take him, John. Kill him after.
如果你能回來
來找我，或許我能讓你成為會員
lf you get back, see me
about membership. Maybe.
好的，我會的
Okay. l will.
- 你在干嘛？
- 祈禱
-What are you doing?
-Praying.
祈禱，好吧
Praying. Okay.
來吧
Come on.
雜种，對嗎？
Half-breeds, right?
他們肯定守護著她，對嗎？
肯定是的
A birth like this, they're definitely
gonna be guarding her, right? Definitely.
對
Yeah.
我們能夠解決他們
我是說，十字架會起作用的，對嗎？
We can get through them. l mean,
that cross has gotta work, right?
對嗎？
Right?
現實和書本不完全一樣
lt's not always like it is in the books.
那是什么？
What is that?
地獄的聲音
Hellspeak.
你知道該怎么做了
You know what to do.
沒問題
l'm okay.
好的
Sure.
最后一次演出
One last show.
嗨
Hi.
我的名字叫約翰
My name's John.
你們破坏了平衡
You are in violation of the balance.
立刻离開
Leave immediately. . .
否則，我將把你們驅逐
. . .or l will deport you.
你們所有的人
All of you.
去死吧
Go to hell.
圣水？
Holy water?
安吉拉
Angela.
約翰？
John?
約翰
John.
媽的
Shit.
拉住！
Pull!
安吉拉
Angela.
安吉拉，怎么了？
Angela, what is it?
把它赶出來
Get it out.
把它……
Get it--
哦，上帝
Oh, my God.
干得不賴，孩子
Not bad, kid.
“干得不賴”
你听到了嗎？
''Not bad. '' You hear that?
知道為什么嗎？因為我是克萊默
查斯·克萊默，混……
You know why that is? lt's because
this is Kramer. Chas Kramer, ass--
查斯
Chas.
你說得沒錯，約翰
You're right, John.
和書上不一樣
lt's not like the books.
不……
No. . .
不一樣
. . .it isn't.
現身吧，我命令你
lnto the light, l command thee.
你的能量令我吃惊
Your ego is astounding.
加百列
Gabriel.
不出所料
Figures.
邪惡將接管地球
And the wicked shall inherit the Earth.
你是在審判我嗎？約翰
You judging me now, John?
背叛，謀殺，种族滅絕
卻說我狹隘
Betrayal, murder, genocide,
call me provincial.
我只是想喚醒人類
讓他們看到后果
l am simply seeking to inspire mankind
to all that was intended.
通過把地球拱手讓給惡魔之子？
By handing Earth over
to the son of the devil?
殺了我吧
Help me here.
你被賦予了這种寶貴的天賦，對嗎？
You're handed this precious gift, right?
造物主允許你們每個人贖罪
Each one of you granted redemption
from the Creator.
殺人犯，強奸犯，性騷扰……
Murderers, rapists and molesters. . .
你們所有這些人
只要忏悔
. . .all of you, you just have to repent. . .
上帝就會伸出雙手迎接你們
. . .and God takes you into his bosom.
茫茫宇宙，大千世界
ln all the worlds in all the universe. . .
除了人類以外
沒有哪种生物能以此為傲
. . .no other creature can make
such a boast, save man.
這不公平
lt's not fair.
如果好心的上帝這么愛你們
lf sweet, sweet God loves you so. . .
那我就要讓你們值得被他愛
. . .then l'll make you worthy of his love.
我盯著你很久了
l've been watching you for a long time.
只有面對恐懼的時候
你才能真正找到你高貴的自我
lt's only in the face of horror
that you truly find your nobler selves.
你才能變得那么的高貴
And you can be so noble.
因此
So. . .
我要給你帶來痛苦
. . .l'll bring you pain.
帶來恐懼
l'll bring you horror.
這樣你才能戰胜它們
So that you may rise above it.
這樣，那些從人間地獄中存活下來的人
So that those of you who survive
this reign of hell on Earth. . .
才值得擁有上帝的愛
. . .will be worthy of God's love.
加百列
Gabriel. . .
你瘋了
. . .you're insane.
拯救將在今晚展開
The road to salvation begins tonight.
就現在
Right now.
我知道你不喜歡我
l know l'm not one of your favorites.
你甚至不歡迎我進你的家門
l'm not even welcome in your house.
我能引起你些許的注意嗎？
But l could use a little attention.
懇求你
Please.
來吧
Come forth.
快點
Hurry.
曼蒙……
Mammon. . .
撒旦之子
. . .son of Satan. . .
我來把你放入這個世界
. . .l unleash you unto this world.
路
Lu.
為什么這么久才來
What took you so long?
你好，約翰
Hello, John.
John, hello.
你的靈魂
You're the one soul. . .
我是一定要親自來收的
. . .l would come up here
to collect myself.
我听說了
So l've heard.
不介意吧？
You mind?
哦，可以，隨意
我有時間
Oh, go-- Go right ahead. l've got stock.
香煙
Coffin nail.
和你很配，約翰
Very fitting, John.
知道嗎，割得太深會割斷肌腱
You know, when you cut too deep,
you cut the tendons. . .
手指就不听使喚了
. . .finger movement goes
out the window.
我來幫你
Let me help you.
看到了嗎？
See?
小寶貝……
Sonny. . .
我為你准備了一整座主題公園
讓你好好快活
. . .l've got a whole theme park
full of red delights for you.
哦，你真好
Well, aren't you a peach.
我想，你不會再犯同樣的錯誤了吧
l didn't think you would
make the same mistake twice.
你不會的
And you didn't. . .
是不是？
. . .did you?
你家里都好嗎？
So how's the family?
很好
忙得要命，需要休個假了
Family's doing just fine.
Busy, busy, busy. Need a vacation.
听說你的孩子和你一個脾气
Word is that kid of yours
is a chip off the old block.
是啊，個頂個的棒
Well, one does what one can.
他就在隔壁
He's in the other room.
男孩就是男孩
Boys will be boys.
和加百列在一起
With Gabriel.
有些愛好真的沒法解釋
No accounting for taste, really.
他們拿著命運之矛
They have the Spear of Destiny.
“他們拿著命運之矛”
''They have the Spear of Destiny. ''
又想和我玩什么花樣？
Or is it another one of your cons?
你自己去看
Go look for yourself.
路，你已經等了我20年
You've waited 20 years for me, Lu. . .
再等20秒又何妨？
. . .what's another 20 seconds?
- 路西法
- 這個世界是我的，幸虧及時赶到
-Lucifer.
-This world is mine. ln time.
你，加百列
作為我們之中最棒的
You, best of all of us, Gabriel. . .
居然也這么有野心
. . .should understand ambition.
毀滅之子
Son of perdition.
小喇叭
Little horn.
最邪惡的人
Most unclean.
真怀念這些舊時的稱呼
l do miss the old names.
該回家了，儿子
Time to go home, son.
我要替上帝
l will smite thee. . .
懲罰你
. . .in his honor.
好像某人不再支持你了
Looks like somebody doesn't
have your back anymore.
父親？
Father?
那么
So.
那么什么
好了，你想要什么？
再給你延期？
Yeah, what do you want? An extension?
她的妹妹
The sister. . .
伊莎貝爾
. . .lsabel.
她怎么了？
What about her?
讓她回家
Let her go home.
你愿意放棄你的生命
讓她升入天堂？
You're willing to give up your life
so she can go to heaven?
好的，可以
Fine. lt's done.
該走了，約翰
Time to go, John.
好的
Yeah.
獻身
The sacrifice.
不，這個人屬于我
No. This one belongs to me.
不，你要活著，約翰·康斯坦丁
No. You will live, John Constantine.
你要活著
You will live.
這樣你才……
So you will have. . .
有机會證明
. . .the chance to prove. . .
你的靈魂是屬于地獄的
. . .that your soul truly belongs in hell.
哦，你要活著
Oh, you will live.
你要活著
You will live.
謝謝你
Thank you.
沒關系
No problem.
人類
Human.
你不應該成為人類
You don't deserve to be human.
你想報仇嗎？
你現在是這么想的嗎？
Do you want revenge?
ls that what you're thinking right now?
來吧
Do it.
來啊
替他們報仇吧
Seek revenge.
殺了我吧
End my life.
來啊
Go on.
替上帝動手吧
Be the hand of God.
這是你的選擇
lt's your choice.
一直都是你的選擇
lt's always been your choice.
好吧
Yeah.
這叫做痛
That's called pain.
學著習慣吧
Get used to it.
你本可以打死我的，約翰！
You could've shot me, John!
你選擇了積德！
You chose a higher path!
看你做得多棒！
Look how well you're doing!
景色不錯
Nice spot.
我有東西要給你
l have something for you.
這樣東西讓我知道
你不是那种華而不實的人
Something tells me
you're not a flowers kind of guy.
哦，你真聰明
Oh, how thoughtful.
約翰
John. . .
為什么給我這個？
. . .why are you giving me this?
這是規則
Rules.
把它藏起來
Hide it.
藏在一個沒人能找到的地方
Somewhere no one
will ever be able to find it.
包括我
Not even me.
就知道沒那么簡單
Always a catch.
是啊
Yeah.
那么
So.
我想洗個澡
l've got some cleaning up to do.
我們……
l'll. . .
再見吧
. . .see you around.
好啊
l'd like that.
我想，我們每個人都自有安排
I guess there's a plan for all of us.
我死了兩次
I had to die...
才明白
... twice...
這個道理
...just to figure that out.
就像書上說的，冥冥中自有安排
Like the book says, he works his work
in mysterious ways.
有些人喜歡
Some people like it...
有些人不喜歡
...some people don 't.
你做得很好，孩子
You did good, kid.
TLF中文字幕站
http://tlfsubs.eastgame.net
Subtitles by
SDl Media Group
[ENGLlSH]